DAVID LUCE



linkedin.com/in/david-luce-80bb41135

393 E 400 N Bountiful UT, 84010 (801) 991-0135 | david.luce@outlook.com

SUMMARY

Experienced Junior Developer with 1-3 years of demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Designed hundreds of websites using HTML, CSS, PHP, CSS, jQuery, JavaScript, and multiple online hosting platforms, helping clients scale their ecommerce stores.

EXPERIENCE

Epic SLC Group/Nutra Drop

Jr. Web Developer/ June 2018-June 2019

Built fully responsive websites, from creation to deployment in collaboration with companies Graphic Designer, and CEO for the purpose of applying for new eCommerce merchant account lines.

Direct Business Lending/Pro-Funding Company

Operations Manager/ May 2017-June 2018 (Direct Business Lending rebranded to Pro-Funding Company)

Sales Manager/ November 2013 – May 2017 (Direct Business Lending)

Set up and maintained all company software, designed and implemented corporate training for sales team allowing company to scale to 100+ employees by the end of 2017.

EDUCATION

Weber State University: AAS in progress of switching to AAT.

University of Utah: Full Stack Developer Coding Bootcamp Certification.

SKILLS/ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Front end software (1-2 Yrs.), HTML5, CSS (1-2 Yrs.) JavaScript (<1 Yr.), jQuery, API, and Bootstrap, Firebase Database, SaaS (1-2 Yrs.). Will acquire- Angular, React and Vue.
- Ability to quickly learn new technologies and maximize their use.
- The National Society of Collegiate Scholars, honor date Jan 2015 WSU; honor issuer NSCS.